<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ProjectPrimaryUsage</string>
    <string name="about_us"> About Us

Greetings from the e-CO2 team!!! It is nice to see you around.

e-CO2 is an app that is designed for our world. We aim to decrease carbon dioxide emissions by calculating our users carbon emission rates and giving them the necessary solution ideas. There will be 5 main parts that you can use in our application. The first one is the home page. It is the initial display page and you can reach all the other parts of our application from here. The bottom icons are just designated for that purpose. From the home page you can access the daily usage page where you can access data about primary usage, secondary usage, monthly calculator, solutions and recycle. Also, there will be monthly and overall usages at the bottom. The Primary Usage button will direct you to the primary usage page. You will enter information about household, natural gas, electricity, lpg and other details. The secondary usage button will direct you to the secondary usage page, where you will be entering nutrition, pharmaceuticals, clothing, paper products, motor vehicles details. The next button is the monthly calculator and there will be the results of your monthly usages. The Solutions button will direct you to the specifically designed solutions for you where you can see what to do in order to protect our world. Lastly from the recycle button you can access a map with some recycle-bin locations so that you can contribute to our environment by recycling. Again from the home page, you can access your profile details such as your name, username, password and profile picture. You can change your name, password and profile picture from the profile page. There will be your rank and score as well. Try to be the winner!!! We unfortunately won’t let you change your username because we don’t want our rankings to change with each username change. There will be multiple colors for you to choose for your profile picture. If you want another color, just contact us :) Lastly, you can see your current rank from our home page, just by clicking on the online button. Not to forget to mention that we have added some articles about nature to enlighten you.  If you have any questions don’t hesitate to contact us!!!

Between 10.00-17.00 : +90 533 509 63 83</string>
</resources>